{"data":[{"question":"He ______ a letter to his friend.","a":"write","b":"writed","c":"written","d":"wrote","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)- Write- wrote- written","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"We haven't ,______ that yet.","a":"tryed","b":"tryied","c":"tryd","d":"tried","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Try - Tried - Tried","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Has the child ______ the medicine?","a":"take","b":"taken","c":"took","d":"taking","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Take - Took - Taken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ to Madrid by plane.","a":"go","b":"goed","c":"went","d":"god","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Go - Went - Gone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you ______ all the bread?","a":"cat","b":"eaten","c":"ate","d":"eating","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Eat - Ate - Eaten","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The little girl ______ the wrong bus.","a":"take","b":"took","c":"taken","d":"taking","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Take - Took - Taken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I _______ some francs in the bank.","a":"change","b":"changed","c":"changes","d":"changing","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Change - Changed - Changed","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It was cheap. It ______ me ","a":"cost","b":"costed","c":"costs","d":"costted","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Cost - Cost - Cost","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I ______ a man in the street.","a":"saw","b":"see","c":"seeing","d":"seed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- See - saw- seen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr Smith has already arrived ______ the office.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","d":"-","answer":"2","explain":"- Arrive in : general location\n- Arrive at: specific location","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}